<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>News on Marvel Rivals</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/categories/news/</link>
    <description>Recent content in News on Marvel Rivals</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 13:45:49 +0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/categories/news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Season 1: New Maps</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/newslist/season1newmaps/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 13:45:49 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/newslist/season1newmaps/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;new-maps-for-season-1-fight-in-new-york-city-on-jan-10th&#34;&gt;New maps for Season 1! Fight in New York City on Jan 10th!&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Two new maps will be added at the coming first half of season 1 for the Empire of Eternal Night in New York City: Sanctum Sanctorum and Midtown&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Keyboard and Mouse Adapters Statement</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/newslist/statement/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 13:45:49 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/newslist/statement/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;keyboard-and-mouse-adapters-statement&#34;&gt;Keyboard and Mouse Adapters Statement&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the wake of the buzz surrounding our recent Dev Vision, where keyboard and mouse adapters were mentioned, we&amp;rsquo;ve seen a surge of interest and questions from our mighty community. We&amp;rsquo;re here to shed some light on this matter.&#xA;First, the Marvel Rivals team stands unwavering in our mission to foster a fair and thrilling gameplay for all. Cheating in any form is something we will battle relentlessly, and we call upon our community to rally behind our quest to maintain a positive gaming atmosphere.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mr Fantastic and Invisible Woman Arriving</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/newslist/newcharactersmrfantastic/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 13:45:49 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/newslist/newcharactersmrfantastic/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;mister-fantastic-and-invisible-woman-join-the-fight-on-jan-10th&#34;&gt;Mister Fantastic and Invisible Woman Join the fight on Jan 10th!&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Darkness engulfs New York as the Timestream Entanglement leaves Doctor Strange trapped in the Entangled Astral Plane, scattering the Darkhold pages. Dracula and Doctor Doom disrupt the moon’s orbit, plunging the city into eternal night and unleashing an army of vampiric creatures. With the world on the brink, the Fantastic Four join forces with iconic Marvel heroes, standing together in the epic battle to break the mystical darkness with science. Ignite the battle against Dracula with the Fantastic Four in Marvel Rivals!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
