<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Marvel Rivals</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Marvel Rivals</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 13:45:49 +0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Season 1: New Maps</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/newslist/season1newmaps/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 13:45:49 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/newslist/season1newmaps/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;new-maps-for-season-1-fight-in-new-york-city-on-jan-10th&#34;&gt;New maps for Season 1! Fight in New York City on Jan 10th!&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Two new maps will be added at the coming first half of season 1 for the Empire of Eternal Night in New York City: Sanctum Sanctorum and Midtown&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Keyboard and Mouse Adapters Statement</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/newslist/statement/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 13:45:49 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/newslist/statement/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;keyboard-and-mouse-adapters-statement&#34;&gt;Keyboard and Mouse Adapters Statement&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the wake of the buzz surrounding our recent Dev Vision, where keyboard and mouse adapters were mentioned, we&amp;rsquo;ve seen a surge of interest and questions from our mighty community. We&amp;rsquo;re here to shed some light on this matter.&#xA;First, the Marvel Rivals team stands unwavering in our mission to foster a fair and thrilling gameplay for all. Cheating in any form is something we will battle relentlessly, and we call upon our community to rally behind our quest to maintain a positive gaming atmosphere.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mr Fantastic and Invisible Woman Arriving</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/newslist/newcharactersmrfantastic/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 13:45:49 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/newslist/newcharactersmrfantastic/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;mister-fantastic-and-invisible-woman-join-the-fight-on-jan-10th&#34;&gt;Mister Fantastic and Invisible Woman Join the fight on Jan 10th!&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Darkness engulfs New York as the Timestream Entanglement leaves Doctor Strange trapped in the Entangled Astral Plane, scattering the Darkhold pages. Dracula and Doctor Doom disrupt the moon’s orbit, plunging the city into eternal night and unleashing an army of vampiric creatures. With the world on the brink, the Fantastic Four join forces with iconic Marvel heroes, standing together in the epic battle to break the mystical darkness with science. Ignite the battle against Dracula with the Fantastic Four in Marvel Rivals!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black Panther</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/herolist/duelist/blackpanther/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2024 13:45:49 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/herolist/duelist/blackpanther/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Black Panther&lt;/strong&gt; T&amp;rsquo;Challa, King of Wakanda, wields the perfect blend of the cutting-edge Vibranium technology and ancestral power drawn from the Panther God, Bast. The Black Panther bides his time until elegantly infiltrating enemy lines and commencing his hunt.Most landsharks are vicious creatures of the deep&amp;hellip; but not Jeff! This adorable and mischievous little landshark brings splashes of joy and healing to every battle. But if the tide turns, Jeff can morph into a voracious beast, swallowing an army of foes in one giant gulp!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Captain America</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/herolist/vanguard/captainamerica/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2024 13:45:49 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/herolist/vanguard/captainamerica/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Captain America&lt;/strong&gt; Enhanced by the Super-Soldier Serum, Steven &amp;ldquo;Steve&amp;rdquo; Rogers uses his Vibranium shield and extensive combat training to confront any threat to justice. When Captain America rallies his troops, a wave of courage sweeps across the battlefield!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doctor Strange</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/herolist/vanguard/doctorstrange/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2024 13:45:49 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/herolist/vanguard/doctorstrange/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Doctor Strange&lt;/strong&gt; As the Sorcerer Supreme, Doctor Stephen Strange gracefully wields ancient spells to turn the tide of even the most impossible battle. However, magic always comes at a cost, and each use of his arcane abilities gradually awakens the darkness within him.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hawkeye</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/herolist/duelist/hawkeye/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2024 13:45:49 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/herolist/duelist/hawkeye/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Black Panther&lt;/strong&gt; Despite his lack of superpowers, Hawkeye&amp;rsquo;s unparalleled skills as a marksman have earned him a spot alongside earth&amp;rsquo;s mightiest heroes. With a cool head and steady hand, Clint Barton never misses a target… so enemies best stay out of his sights!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hulk</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/herolist/vanguard/hulk/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2024 13:45:49 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/herolist/vanguard/hulk/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hulk&lt;/strong&gt; Brilliant scientist Dr. Bruce Banner has finally found a way to coexist with his monstrous alter ego, the Hulk. By accumulating gamma energy over multiple transformations, he can become a wise and strong Hero Hulk or a fierce and destructive Monster Hulk – a true force of fury on the battlefield!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IronMan</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/herolist/duelist/ironman/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2024 13:45:49 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/herolist/duelist/ironman/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Iron Man&lt;/strong&gt; Armed with superior intellect and a nanotech battlesuit of his own design, Tony Stark stands alongside gods as the Invincible Iron Man. His state of the art armor turns any battlefield into his personal playground, allowing him to steal the spotlight he so desperately desires.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jeff The Land Shark</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/herolist/strategist/jeffthelandshark/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2024 13:45:49 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/herolist/strategist/jeffthelandshark/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jeff The Land Shark&lt;/strong&gt; Most landsharks are vicious creatures of the deep&amp;hellip; but not Jeff! This adorable and mischievous little landshark brings splashes of joy and healing to every battle. But if the tide turns, Jeff can morph into a voracious beast, swallowing an army of foes in one giant gulp!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Luna Snow</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/herolist/strategist/lunasnow/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2024 13:45:49 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/herolist/strategist/lunasnow/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Luna Snow&lt;/strong&gt; Equal parts pop star and Super Hero, Luna Snow puts on a dazzling show with both her light and dark ice powers. The arena is her stage, where Seol Hee and her team orchestrate spectacular displays that earn her an ever-increasing number of fans and wins.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rocket Raccoon</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/herolist/strategist/rocketraccoon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2024 13:45:49 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/herolist/strategist/rocketraccoon/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rocket Raccoon&lt;/strong&gt; Rocket may not look like a tech genius or an expert tactician, but anyone who&amp;rsquo;s ever made his hit list has quickly regretted underestimating him. This savvy space soldier is equally eager to boost his teammates and to collect bounties on his foes.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
